<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Lual Dev]]></title><description><![CDATA[Web development blog.]]></description><link>https://lual.dev</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 14:19:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Holamundo]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello world! I finally started writing and I hope to be able to keep doing so on a consistent basis. This is not the first blog that I start…]]></description><link>https://lual.dev/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://lual.dev/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 01:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hello world! I finally started writing and I hope to be able to keep doing so on a consistent basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not the first blog that I start, but it is the first one that gets me as excited as I am with this new venture. It probably has to do with having a more mature set of interests now, and knowing that programming and in particular, web development is one of the most important items in that set.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s in it for you&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you happen to have a keen interest in solving interesting problems using Javascript, Python and related technologies, while being as effective and productive as possible, then, chances are that you’ll find something of value here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll be documenting new things I learn in my personal journey as a developer, and I’ll make my best to provide as much value as possible in every post I write.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this looks like something you’d like to keep an eye on, you can do so following &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lualdev/&quot;&gt;@lualdev on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll be posting weekly-ish, see you in the next post! :).&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>